[PLAYING RED HOT CH ILI PEPPERS'
"UNDER THE BRIDGE"]
[SINGING]
And I don't ever wanna feel
Like I did that day
Take me to the place I love
Take me all the way
[SINGING IN FALSETTO]
And I don't ever wanna feel
Like I did that day
Take me to the place I love...
[SQUEALS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
(Penny:)Fellas, please.
(Howard:)Penny, come on.
We were just finding our sound.
(Penny:)You found it. It's the sound of a cat
being run over by a lawn mower.
Well, I'm really very busy.
Is there any way we can put this off
until I have more time to prepare?
(Leonard(entering on the phone):)Of course,
but, uh, you understand my trepidation.
- What's that about?
- Not a clue.
(Leonard:)Can't we just postpone it till the spring?
(Leonard:)Maybe next summer?
(Sheldon:)This should be fairly easy to deduce.
(Sheldon:)He's holding the phone to his left ear.
Ears do not cross hemispheres.